Hey guys, what is up Marcus here from WaveHub?
I wanted to analyze a game with you today. This is gonna be Jodar against Lehecka
Jodar with the hype that he all has right now and he's going into the top 20s
Or he's already in top 20s looking to actually go at the place 11 or 12 after this win
So Lehecka is
Place 12 and ATP very established top 20 player. So yeah, we're gonna analyze this game
50 minutes. This will also be a game that I'm gonna
I'm gonna be giving to my community
So you can a little bit see how I'm analyzing those matches
So let's just get started. The first step I always like to go on Flashscore and look at the
matches
Because we already have here on the most tournaments a very good breakdown of the match
So you should always read this and take the things into consideration
So what they are basically doing is they have news and form so
You can read into that. That's very nicely written
If they had to had the stats in fact,
so also that Jodar is unbeaten and masters around 16
Driven Rome this year Lehecka has a native friend code of 6 to 13 against the 20 class.
It's also very important
Well, Jodar is 2 in 2
so also this year's formula masters is 4 to 60 masters and
2 1 this year so betting analysis actually says
Expect a close high quality top 20 better with current home green Jodar a slight edge heading
into the match
So this already up front gives you a good feeling on how the match will be because flash
score has a lot of data
So they do know what they're doing
So you can also take this into consideration, but just read don't take it for granted
Next up what I always like to do because I'm not analyzing all the matches just based on
My WaveHub bot so what what this bot does is basically scanning for the odds that are being
released
So this is a tool you would get
in the gold program you are getting
all the odds that are being played and
Already calculated with our models. You can actually see if there's value going on.
What's the opening odd and what is
What is happening in the ATP? So I just get the notification that the odds are out and we
have
few symbols here it just
quickly to go to explain
Exclamation work is basically
Something's wrong. There's probably an injury going on or injury doubts or fitness doubts
so
For example, Darderi here has the odds of 2.4, but he should have a pair out of two
So it's a 22% edge against Borges
So it's it's a game I would not touch because you actually already have the information that
Darderi is
Saying that he has something with his feet that he's not really feeling well
So that's why I'm skipping those matches
Sometimes those are true the edges, but it's really you have to be careful with that one
So then why I'm analyzing these matches. We already have like the green light here
Which is like good values is above 5% edge compared to model
So Jodar should have an auto 4.7 and he actually does with my model at 1.83
That's 8% edge. So that's always what we're targeting like at least 5% edge.
That's why I established that symbol
So that's what you should look out for. So those two matches you can actually
Look into I mean team versus Tyrande was actually,
you know, it's pretty low also
I would not take it like a single
But yeah, then we have like slight value where you have to be like
Really careful if you want to take this most of the times it doesn't really make sense
Except you're playing like, you know, I'll try it or something
But also here we have no value
So it like you have like winners you can take him as a winner if you really think that he's
gonna win
But usually if you want to be profitable in the long term usually it don't take
Odds are not profitable and really take in Nakashima is a question mark
Because it's high risk. So, you know, usually you have like odds then around 2.5 3 4
So that's where you're getting edges really fast
And you know, that's always a little bit
You have to be careful with that
so, okay, so we already seen the odd 1.8 3 3
which
Is correlating with my model. So this is the pinnacle odd fair odds
We have a 7.8 percent of edge here
So what I like to do is I like to look at both players individually
So so you can go down here and what
you see is the match record this year
So he's 12 and 7 in hard. He had very solid
Results here. So
One title no time so far here
Five and five in clay. So you can say that it's probably not as good as 2025
So he's a little bit struggling
Looking at the matches he's played
He actually lost the first round
Pretty shockingly against Wong. So that's that's always something like you have to analyze
what went wrong there
But it's just the first
Hardcore match and then actually that's why he gets the favor the most he won against Coppejans
and blocks
Which are both mediocre players in my opinion. So if you look at Coppejans
He's ranked 71
If you look at the stats at his last match
He was really bad serving as you can see here 57 and 58% usually you would want that around
86%
because you have a good serve and can hold that but
Yes, the Coppejans is actually a mediocre player as well as blocks was really not impressive
during the match
But we're gonna come to that later
so
Yeah
Also, really not impressive looking just that's here
What I'm looking out for is break points saved so you can see how dominant the game actually
was you can also see that
By point by point so you can have a look like how many times there were the break opportunities
For example here it was the serve of lechka,
but he did face two break points and then the set just carried on
So not really dominant. I would say my case was just one break and their blocks had the chance
to re break
Looking at the set to
long first
Long first game with two potential break points and also here and blocks just kind of get
weaker
Points were really short. So
Was really a dominant display. I would say
Choder
Right
Right, so when we look at shoulder,
he obviously has a lot of high P. He was really not that good against a muttee
Did struggle a little bit
So he shouldn't have struggled but muttee is always the kind of player that gets you
You know that gets you kind of
Get just gets you struggling because muttee is always has very very nice varieties of his
tennis, but he's of course not
Consistent at all. So it was just a six double four was also really not good
Also a lot of break points face. So that's why why most of
The people I was talking with already faded him because like he was just participating at
the final
Then of course, you have to say he's pretty young. So he will recover rather fast and
When we look at this match, which is really interesting the double falls pretty much went
down
Didn't face a lot of break points. You know, most of these are better opponent and muttee
Obviously second serve points were also pretty low. So
That's definitely a very interesting point and 19 winners 22 unforced arrows is a good ratio
and
Yes, it was over. You can really say now
You would think that lechka is better player,
but obviously children has Facebook steady, which is a top 10 top 20 player
so
We can really distinguish now if is the value
Worth the risk that I want to take
So we're gonna have to dig deeper and also look at it objectively all the time
So again, we have the 8% edge, but do we want to play a percent edge?
That just makes sense. You need to have some reasons to actually back this
Because all of this data would say it's pretty much equal
the public opinion goes a little bit towards lechka as
Yeah, we're gonna go to the leader though
Let's go. What I also like to do after I compared the stats.
So the stats I just shared you
I always like to look at some articles. So when we look at this
It's last word and sports. It's a really good source.
I like this one. If we're just going down to
Lehecka
Let's just read this real quick
Yeah, should be
Should be tight
shoulder in freeze to prediction
Also on X or let me just look for
lechka shoulder
prediction just a little bit to get a little bit more source
Edge over wins, but not really explanation to that
Over 2.5 sets. So a lot of people are pointing towards that it will be a closed game
Chose the odd signals
So what I also like to do is just to have a look on on the game. So
Um, it was the last games that they played
actually looking for
How they played was it unforced errors or was it just lechka being good?
All right,
you can always look at the highlights
um
I also really think that um, you can read out of the the people like how they play a lot
But again, it's just all evolves around the
around the
Value that's being created with the model because you have to stick to that
And then you can actually see do I like this bet or do I not like this bet?
And based on the value even if you just go for the value
You should be able to get profitable in the long term if you can hold your emotions and if
you're patient
But it's always the case that you should like do more research to find more confluences
So if lechka is blocks, sorry
You can see it's 40 30
Backhand aggressive backhand down the line
Also here again very solid
playing for the edges
Very solid from blocks
So not a lot of unforced errors. We can see
That she gets very aggressive coming to the net
Really often
But what's actually interesting what we will see against shoulder.
So here's a big up first error like what was that?
um
What we can what we will see at shoulder is um that he will attack the backhand with his
cross backhand way more
So that's actually where it will be interesting to see how how lechka will react to that
So just watch the backhand from lechka, right?
So this was like at the baseline in set out
At the baseline
It's not very precise or aggressive. He goes red to a defense mode
Okay, that was gifted
um
So the backhand side is always going into defense mode,
which I think shoulder will attack like pretty pretty well
So he's really just taking forehand cross a lot of times and backhand down the line
That was really pretty
First error it was match
So I don't think blocks was really appropriate measure
For him very much the favorite. I do believe lechka is strong, but he
He does struggle with consistency
Like when we go back when we go
back
to the match
lechka
Qualifier previous. I didn't have a real challenge until yet
meanwhile, um
shoulder had moselli, which
Mutei, which is a pretty tricky player also moselli, which is a very
Good player. He was very consistent hard court likes hard court murrow and he's a top 20
player
so, um
Yeah, guys, I
after all that I've researched
I would definitely be into words, um
shoulder as I believe I believe in the value that that I was created
um, I also noted
looking at the career
of
Looking at the career of lechka
second
So what were the
What were good progresses or what was this year for him like?
Uh, if we're going down to the start of the year
You know, he lost against gea at the australian open
One
That was davis cup. So can we count that one?
Also, he lost against few to the first opponent that is actually in the top 20
he's losing feels
all year
um
He did win against fritz here in miami. So that was pretty big win
Uh, one against fields here
So that was against buble. You know, that was all clay season. So it didn't really play a
lot
this year
I guess noria exhibition that was grass
Another hard court season started again. So really see lechka losing here.
Also in my preview what I um
Where I break down the whole draw
until you basically insert
you can
You can take for your bets. Um
I was also talking a lot about shoulder
Uh, I put him as a dark horse as he has a very very good way through here
So we're here
and
I'm very excited to see what he will bring here possibly going for a long shot to in the
quarter
minimum price around six or seven
cocketed with a model
So also a quick summary at the bottom
This was one of my picks to
for him to win
shoulder and for him to win against mosedi
so
that was um
Yeah, if you if you stick to a plan you will always find a way
So also like michelson or it's like both of them
Uh, we're out of the tournament, but that's also what I wrote down here.
Of course, it can change
So it can always change that would just potentially run free matchups that I would like to
have to target
um
Man sick to win against kachanov. So kachanov is already out shoulder is doing rubles if
the rubles the very much I would have been
um
Would have been there. Um, so yeah
Shoulder are very positive on this one. I will take the bet life with you
So I will stick my two percent of bankroll
um
And yeah, so there's money line
1.833
so I'm gonna
Place that bet and
Yeah, we will see each other after the game